NAME
    gcloud beta run deploy - create or update a Cloud Run service

SYNOPSIS
    gcloud beta run deploy [[SERVICE] --namespace=NAMESPACE]
        [--[no-]allow-unauthenticated] [--async] [--breakglass=JUSTIFICATION]
        [--clear-vpc-connector] [--concurrency=CONCURRENCY]
        [--container=CONTAINER] [--[no-]cpu-boost] [--[no-]cpu-throttling]
        [--[no-]default-url] [--[no-]deploy-health-check]
        [--description=DESCRIPTION]
        [--execution-environment=EXECUTION_ENVIRONMENT] [--gpu-type=GPU_TYPE]
        [--[no-]gpu-zonal-redundancy] [--[no-]iap]
        [--ingress=INGRESS; default="all"] [--[no-]invoker-iam-check]
        [--max=MAX] [--max-instances=MAX_INSTANCES] [--mesh=MESH] [--min=MIN]
        [--min-instances=MIN_INSTANCES] [--region=REGION] [--regions=REGIONS]
        [--remove-containers=[CONTAINER,...]]
        [--revision-suffix=REVISION_SUFFIX] [--scaling=SCALING]
        [--service-account=SERVICE_ACCOUNT] [--[no-]session-affinity]
        [--tag=TAG] [--timeout=TIMEOUT] [--no-traffic]
        [--vpc-connector=VPC_CONNECTOR] [--vpc-egress=VPC_EGRESS]
        [--add-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]
          | --clear-cloudsql-instances
          | --remove-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]
          | --set-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]]
        [--add-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]
          | --clear-custom-audiences
          | --remove-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]
          | --set-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]]
        [--add-volume=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          --clear-volumes --remove-volume=[VOLUME,...]]
        [--add-volume-mount=[volume=NAME,mount-path=MOUNT_PATH,...]
          --args=[ARG,...] --[no-]automatic-updates --clear-volume-mounts
          --cpu=CPU --depends-on=[CONTAINER,...] --gpu=GPU
          --liveness-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...] --memory=MEMORY --port=PORT
          --readiness-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          --remove-volume-mount=[MOUNT_PATH,...]
          --startup-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          --[no-]use-http2 --base-image=BASE_IMAGE
          | --clear-base-image --build-env-vars-file=FILE_PATH
          | --clear-build-env-vars | --set-build-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          | --remove-build-env-vars=[KEY,...]
          --update-build-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          --build-service-account=BUILD_SERVICE_ACCOUNT
          | --clear-build-service-account --build-worker-pool=BUILD_WORKER_POOL
          | --clear-build-worker-pool --clear-env-vars
          | --env-vars-file=FILE_PATH | --set-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          | --remove-env-vars=[KEY,...]
          --update-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...] --clear-secrets
          | --set-secrets=[KEY=VALUE,...] | --remove-secrets=[KEY,...]
          --update-secrets=[KEY=VALUE,...] --command=[COMMAND,...]
          | --function=FUNCTION --image=IMAGE --source=SOURCE]
        [--binary-authorization=POLICY | --clear-binary-authorization]
        [--clear-encryption-key-shutdown-hours
          | --encryption-key-shutdown-hours=ENCRYPTION_KEY_SHUTDOWN_HOURS]
        [--clear-key | --key=KEY]
        [--clear-labels | --remove-labels=[KEY,...] --labels=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          | --update-labels=[KEY=VALUE,...]]
        [--clear-network
          | --network=NETWORK --subnet=SUBNET --clear-network-tags
          | --network-tags=[TAG,...]]
        [--clear-post-key-revocation-action-type
          | --post-key-revocation-action-type=POST_KEY_REVOCATION_ACTION_TYPE]
        [GCLOUD_WIDE_FLAG ...]

DESCRIPTION
    (BETA) Creates or updates a Cloud Run service.

EXAMPLES
    To deploy a container to the service my-backend on Cloud Run:

        $ gcloud beta run deploy my-backend \
          --image=us-docker.pkg.dev/project/image

    You may also omit the service name. Then a prompt will be displayed with a
    suggested default value:

        $ gcloud beta run deploy --image=us-docker.pkg.dev/project/image

    To deploy to Cloud Run on Kubernetes Engine, you need to specify a cluster:

        $ gcloud beta run deploy --image=us-docker.pkg.dev/project/image \
          --cluster=my-cluster

POSITIONAL ARGUMENTS
     Service resource - Service to deploy to. The arguments in this group can
     be used to specify the attributes of this resource.

       [SERVICE]
          ID of the service or fully qualified identifier for the service.

          To set the service attribute:
          + provide the argument SERVICE on the command line;
          + specify the service name from an interactive prompt.

       --namespace=NAMESPACE
          Specific to Cloud Run for Anthos: Kubernetes namespace for the
          service.

          To set the namespace attribute:
          + provide the argument SERVICE on the command line with a fully
            specified name;
          + specify the service name from an interactive prompt with a fully
            specified name;
          + provide the argument --namespace on the command line;
          + set the property run/namespace;
          + For Cloud Run on Kubernetes Engine, defaults to "default".
            Otherwise, defaults to project ID.;
          + provide the argument project on the command line;
          + set the property core/project.

FLAGS
     --[no-]allow-unauthenticated
        Whether to enable allowing unauthenticated access to the service. This
        may take a few moments to take effect. Use --allow-unauthenticated to
        enable and --no-allow-unauthenticated to disable.

     --async
        Return immediately, without waiting for the operation in progress to
        complete.

     --breakglass=JUSTIFICATION
        Justification to bypass Binary Authorization policy constraints and
        allow the operation. See
        https://cloud.google.com/binary-authorization/docs/using-breakglass for
        more information. Next update or deploy command will automatically
        clear existing breakglass justification.

     --clear-vpc-connector
        Remove the VPC connector for this resource.

     --concurrency=CONCURRENCY
        Set the maximum number of concurrent requests allowed per container
        instance. Leave concurrency unspecified or provide the special value
        'default' to receive the server default value.

     --container=CONTAINER
        Specifies a container by name. Flags following --container will apply
        to the specified container.

        Flags that are not container-specific must be specified before
        --container.

     --[no-]cpu-boost
        Whether to allocate extra CPU to containers on startup to reduce the
        perceived latency of a cold start request. Enabled by default when
        unspecified on new services. Use --cpu-boost to enable and
        --no-cpu-boost to disable.

     --[no-]cpu-throttling
        Whether to throttle the CPU when the container is not actively serving
        requests. Use --cpu-throttling to enable and --no-cpu-throttling to
        disable.

     --[no-]default-url
        Toggles the default url for a run service. This is enabled by default
        if not specified. Use --default-url to enable and --no-default-url to
        disable.

     --[no-]deploy-health-check
        Schedules a single instance of the Revision and waits for it to pass
        its startup probe for the deployment to succeed. If disabled, the
        startup probe runs only when the revision is first started via
        invocation or by setting min-instances. This check is enabled by
        default when unspecified. Use --deploy-health-check to enable and
        --no-deploy-health-check to disable.

     --description=DESCRIPTION
        Provides an optional, human-readable description of the service.

     --execution-environment=EXECUTION_ENVIRONMENT
        Selects the execution environment where the application will run.
        EXECUTION_ENVIRONMENT must be one of:

         gen1
            Run the application in a first generation execution environment.
         gen2
            Run the application in a second generation execution environment.

     --gpu-type=GPU_TYPE
        The GPU type to use.

     --[no-]gpu-zonal-redundancy
        Set GPU zonal redundancy. Use --gpu-zonal-redundancy to enable and
        --no-gpu-zonal-redundancy to disable.

     --[no-]iap
        Whether to enable IAP for the Service. Use --iap to enable and --no-iap
        to disable.

     --ingress=INGRESS; default="all"
        Set the ingress traffic sources allowed to call the service. For Cloud
        Run the --[no-]allow-unauthenticated flag separately controls the
        identities allowed to call the service. INGRESS must be one of:

         all
            Inbound requests from all sources are allowed.
         internal
            For Cloud Run, only inbound requests from VPC networks in the same
            project or VPC Service Controls perimeter, as well as Pub/Sub
            subscriptions and Eventarc events in the same project or VPC
            Service Controls perimeter are allowed. All other requests are
            rejected. See https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/securing/ingress
            for full details on the definition of internal traffic for Cloud
            Run.

         internal-and-cloud-load-balancing
            Only inbound requests from Google Cloud Load Balancing or a traffic
            source allowed by the internal option are allowed.

     --[no-]invoker-iam-check
        Optionally disable invoker IAM checks. This feature is available by
        invitation only. More info at
        https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/securing/managing-access#invoker_check.
        Use --invoker-iam-check to enable and --no-invoker-iam-check to
        disable.

     --max=MAX
        The maximum number of container instances to run for this Service. This
        instance limit will be divided among all Revisions receiving a
        percentage of traffic and can be modified without deploying a new
        Revision.

     --max-instances=MAX_INSTANCES
        The maximum number of container instances for this Revision to run or
        'default' to remove. This setting is immutably set on each new Revision
        and modifying its value will deploy another Revision.

     --mesh=MESH
        Enables Cloud Service Mesh using the specified mesh resource name. Mesh
        resource name must be in the format of
        projects/PROJECT/locations/global/meshes/MESH_NAME or MESH_NAME. Will
        default to the current project if only MESH_NAME is provided.

     --min=MIN
        The minimum number of container instances to run for this Service or
        'default' to remove. These instances will be divided among all
        Revisions receiving a percentage of traffic and can be modified without
        deploying a new Revision.

     --min-instances=MIN_INSTANCES
        The minimum number of container instances to run for this Revision or
        'default' to remove. This setting is immutably set on each new Revision
        and modifying its value will deploy a another Revision. Consider using
        --min to set the minimum number of instances across all revisions of
        the Service which may be modified dynamically.

     --region=REGION
        Region in which the resource can be found. Alternatively, set the
        property [run/region].

     --regions=REGIONS
        Comma-separated list of regions in which the multi-region Service can
        be found.

     --remove-containers=[CONTAINER,...]
        List of containers to remove.

     --revision-suffix=REVISION_SUFFIX
        Specify the suffix of the revision name. Revision names always start
        with the service name automatically. For example, specifying
        [--revision-suffix=v1] for a service named 'helloworld', would lead to
        a revision named 'helloworld-v1'. Set empty string to clear the suffix
        and resume server-assigned naming.

     --scaling=SCALING
        The scaling mode to use for this resource. Flag value could be either
        "auto" for automatic scaling, or a positive integer to configure manual
        scaling with the given integer as a fixed instance count.

     --service-account=SERVICE_ACCOUNT
        the email address of an IAM service account associated with the
        revision of the service. The service account represents the identity of
        the running revision, and determines what permissions the revision has.

     --[no-]session-affinity
        Whether to enable session affinity for connections to the service. Use
        --session-affinity to enable and --no-session-affinity to disable.

     --tag=TAG
        Traffic tag to assign to the newly created revision.

     --timeout=TIMEOUT
        Set the maximum request execution time (timeout). It is specified as a
        duration; for example, "10m5s" is ten minutes, and five seconds. If you
        don't specify a unit, seconds is assumed. For example, "10" is 10
        seconds.

     --no-traffic
        True to avoid sending traffic to the revision being deployed. Setting
        this flag assigns any traffic assigned to the LATEST revision to the
        specific revision bound to LATEST before the deployment. The effect is
        that the revision being deployed will not receive traffic.

        After a deployment with this flag the LATEST revision will not receive
        traffic on future deployments. To restore sending traffic to the LATEST
        revision by default, run the gcloud run services update-traffic command
        with --to-latest.

     --vpc-connector=VPC_CONNECTOR
        Set a VPC connector for this resource.

     --vpc-egress=VPC_EGRESS
        Specify which of the outbound traffic to send through Direct VPC egress
        or the VPC connector for this resource. This resource must have Direct
        VPC egress enabled or a VPC connector to set this flag. VPC_EGRESS must
        be one of:

         all
            (DEPRECATED) Sends all outbound traffic through Direct VPC egress
            or the VPC connector. Provides the same functionality as
            'all-traffic'. Prefer to use 'all-traffic' instead.
         all-traffic
            Sends all outbound traffic through Direct VPC egress or the VPC
            connector.
         private-ranges-only
            Default option. Sends outbound traffic to private IP addresses (RFC
            1918 and Private Google Access IPs) through Direct VPC egress or
            the VPC connector.

            Traffic to other Cloud Run services might require additional
            configuration. See
            https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/securing/private-networking#send_requests_to_other_services_and_services
            for more information.

     These flags modify the Cloud SQL instances this Service connects to. You
     can specify a name of a Cloud SQL instance if it's in the same project and
     region as your Cloud Run service; otherwise specify
     <project>:<region>:<instance> for the instance.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --add-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]
          Append the given values to the current Cloud SQL instances.

       --clear-cloudsql-instances
          Empty the current Cloud SQL instances.

       --remove-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]
          Remove the given values from the current Cloud SQL instances.

       --set-cloudsql-instances=[CLOUDSQL-INSTANCES,...]
          Completely replace the current Cloud SQL instances with the given
          values.

     These flags modify the custom audiences that can be used in the audience
     field of ID token for authenticated requests.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --add-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]
          Append the given values to the current custom audiences.

       --clear-custom-audiences
          Empty the current custom audiences.

       --remove-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]
          Remove the given values from the current custom audiences.

       --set-custom-audiences=[CUSTOM-AUDIENCES,...]
          Completely replace the current custom audiences with the given
          values.

     --add-volume=[KEY=VALUE,...]
        Adds a volume to the Cloud Run resource. To add more than one volume,
        specify this flag multiple times. Volumes must have a name and type
        key. Only certain values are supported for type. Depending on the
        provided type, other keys will be required. The following types are
        supported with the specified additional keys:

        cloud-storage: A volume representing a Cloud Storage bucket. This
        volume type is mounted using Cloud Storage FUSE. See
        https://cloud.google.com/storage/docs/gcs-fuse for the details and
        limitations of this filesystem. Additional keys:
        * bucket: (required) the name of the bucket to use as the source of
          this volume
        * readonly: (optional) A boolean. If true, this volume will be
          read-only from all mounts.
        * mount-options: (optional) A list of flags to pass to GCSFuse. Flags
          should be specified without leading dashes and separated by
          semicolons.

        in-memory: An ephemeral volume that stores data in the instance's
        memory. With this type of volume, data is not shared between instances
        and all data will be lost when the instance it is on is terminated.
        Additional keys:
        * size-limit: (optional) A quantity representing the maximum amount
          of memory allocated to this volume, such as "512Mi" or "3G". Data
          stored in an in-memory volume consumes the memory allocation of the
          container that wrote the data. If size-limit is not specified, the
          maximum size will be half the total memory limit of all containers.

        nfs: Represents a volume backed by an NFS server. Additional keys:
        * location: (required) The location of the NFS Server, in the form
          SERVER:/PATH
        * readonly: (optional) A boolean. If true, this volume will be
          read-only from all mounts.

     --clear-volumes
        Remove all existing volumes from the Cloud Run resource, including
        volumes mounted as secrets

     --remove-volume=[VOLUME,...]
        Removes volumes from the Cloud Run resource.

    Container Flags

    The following flags apply to a single container. If the --container flag is
    specified these flags may only be specified after a --container flag.
    Otherwise they will apply to the primary ingress container.

         --add-volume-mount=[volume=NAME,mount-path=MOUNT_PATH,...]
            Adds a mount to the current container. Must contain the keys
            volume=NAME and mount-path=/PATH where NAME is the name of a volume
            on this resource and PATH is the path within the container's
            filesystem to mount this volume.

         --args=[ARG,...]
            Comma-separated arguments passed to the command run by the
            container image. If not specified and no '--command' is provided,
            the container image's default Cmd is used. Otherwise, if not
            specified, no arguments are passed. To reset this field to its
            default, pass an empty string.

         --[no-]automatic-updates
            Indicates whether automatic base image updates should be enabled
            for an image built from source. Use --automatic-updates to enable
            and --no-automatic-updates to disable.

         --clear-volume-mounts
            Remove all existing mounts from the current container.

         --cpu=CPU
            Set a CPU limit in Kubernetes cpu units.

            Cloud Run supports values fractional values below 1, 1, 2, 4, and
            8. Some CPU values requires a minimum Memory --memory value.

         --depends-on=[CONTAINER,...]
            List of container dependencies to add to the current container.

         --gpu=GPU
            Cloud Run supports values 0 or 1. 1 gpu also requires a minimum 4
            --cpu value and a minimum 16Gi --memory value.

         --liveness-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...]
            Comma separated settings for liveness probe in the form KEY=VALUE.
            Each key stands for a field of the probe described in
            https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/reference/rest/v1/Container#Probe.
            Currently supported keys are: initialDelaySeconds, timeoutSeconds,
            periodSeconds, failureThreshold, httpGet.port, httpGet.path,
            grpc.port, grpc.service.

            For example, to set a probe with 10s timeout and HTTP probe
            requests sent to 8080 port of the container:

                $ --liveness-probe=timeoutSeconds=10,httpGet.port=8080

            To remove existing probe:

                $ --liveness-probe=""

         --memory=MEMORY
            Set a memory limit. Ex: 1024Mi, 4Gi.

         --port=PORT
            Container port to receive requests at. Also sets the $PORT
            environment variable. Must be a number between 1 and 65535,
            inclusive. To unset this field, pass the special value "default".
            If updating an existing service with a TCP startup probe pointing
            to the previous container port, this will also update the probe
            port.

         --readiness-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...]
            Comma separated settings for readiness probe in the form KEY=VALUE.
            Each key stands for a field of the probe described in
            https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/reference/rest/v1/Container#Probe.
            Currently supported keys are: timeoutSeconds, periodSeconds,
            failureThreshold, successThreshold, httpGet.port, httpGet.path,
            grpc.port, grpc.service.

            For example, to set a probe with 10s timeout and HTTP probe
            requests sent to 8080 port of the container:

                $ --readiness-probe=timeoutSeconds=10,httpGet.port=8080

            To remove existing probe:

                $ --readiness-probe=""

         --remove-volume-mount=[MOUNT_PATH,...]
            Removes the volume mounted at the specified path from the current
            container.

         --startup-probe=[KEY=VALUE,...]
            Comma separated settings for startup probe in the form KEY=VALUE.
            Each key stands for a field of the probe described in
            https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/reference/rest/v1/Container#Probe.
            Currently supported keys are: initialDelaySeconds, timeoutSeconds,
            periodSeconds, failureThreshold, httpGet.port, httpGet.path,
            grpc.port, grpc.service, tcpSocket.port.

            For example, to set a probe with 10s timeout and HTTP probe
            requests sent to 8080 port of the container:

                $ --startup-probe=timeoutSeconds=10,httpGet.port=8080

            To remove existing probe:

                $ --startup-probe=""

         --[no-]use-http2
            Whether to use HTTP/2 for connections to the service. Use
            --use-http2 to enable and --no-use-http2 to disable.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --base-image=BASE_IMAGE
              Specifies the base image to be used for automatic base image
              updates. When deploying from source using the Google Cloud
              buildpacks, this flag will also override the base image used for
              the application image. See
              https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/configuring/services/automatic-base-image-updates
              for more details.

           --clear-base-image
              Opts out of automatic base image updates.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --build-env-vars-file=FILE_PATH
              Path to a local YAML file with definitions for all build
              environment variables. All existing build environment variables
              will be removed before the new build environment variables are
              added. Example YAML content:

                  KEY_1: "value1"
                  KEY_2: "value 2"

           --clear-build-env-vars
              Remove all build environment variables.

           --set-build-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
              List of key-value pairs to set as build environment variables.
              All existing build environment variables will be removed first.

           Only --update-build-env-vars and --remove-build-env-vars can be used
           together. If both are specified, --remove-build-env-vars will be
           applied first.

             --remove-build-env-vars=[KEY,...]
                List of build environment variables to be removed.

             --update-build-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
                List of key-value pairs to set as build environment variables.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --build-service-account=BUILD_SERVICE_ACCOUNT
              Specifies the service account to use to execute the build.
              Applies only to source deploy builds using the Build API.

           --clear-build-service-account
              Clears the Cloud Build service account field.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --build-worker-pool=BUILD_WORKER_POOL
              Name of the Cloud Build Custom Worker Pool that should be used to
              build the function. The format of this field is
              projects/${PROJECT}/locations/${LOCATION}/workerPools/${WORKERPOOL}
              where ${PROJECT} is the project id and ${LOCATION} is the
              location where the worker pool is defined and ${WORKERPOOL} is
              the short name of the worker pool.

           --clear-build-worker-pool
              Clears the Cloud Build Custom Worker Pool field.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --clear-env-vars
              Remove all environment variables.

           --env-vars-file=FILE_PATH
              Path to a local YAML or ENV file with definitions for all
              environment variables. All existing environment variables will be
              removed before the new environment variables are added. Example
              YAML content:

                  KEY_1: "value1"
                  KEY_2: "value 2"
                  Example ENV content:

                  KEY_1="value1"
                  KEY_2="value 2"

           --set-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
              List of key-value pairs to set as environment variables. All
              existing environment variables will be removed first.

           Only --update-env-vars and --remove-env-vars can be used together.
           If both are specified, --remove-env-vars will be applied first.

             --remove-env-vars=[KEY,...]
                List of environment variables to be removed.

             --update-env-vars=[KEY=VALUE,...]
                List of key-value pairs to set as environment variables.

         Specify secrets to mount or provide as environment variables. Keys
         starting with a forward slash '/' are mount paths. All other keys
         correspond to environment variables. Values should be in the form
         SECRET_NAME:SECRET_VERSION. For example:
         '--update-secrets=/secrets/api/key=mysecret:latest,ENV=othersecret:1'
         will mount a volume at '/secrets/api' containing a file 'key' with the
         latest version of secret 'mysecret'. An environment variable named ENV
         will also be created whose value is version 1 of secret 'othersecret'.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --clear-secrets
              Remove all secrets.

           --set-secrets=[KEY=VALUE,...]
              List of key-value pairs to set as secrets. All existing secrets
              will be removed first.

           Only --update-secrets and --remove-secrets can be used together. If
           both are specified, --remove-secrets will be applied first.

             --remove-secrets=[KEY,...]
                List of secrets to be removed.

             --update-secrets=[KEY=VALUE,...]
                List of key-value pairs to set as secrets.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --command=[COMMAND,...]
              Entrypoint for the container image. If not specified, the
              container image's default Entrypoint is run. To reset this field
              to its default, pass an empty string.

           --function=FUNCTION
              Specifies that the deployed object is a function. If a value is
              provided, that value is used as the entrypoint.

         --image=IMAGE
            Name of the container image to deploy (e.g.
            us-docker.pkg.dev/cloudrun/container/hello:latest). When used with
            --source, the image must be the URI of an Artifact Registry Docker
            repository in the Docker format
            ($REGION-docker.pkg.dev/$PROJECT/$REPOSITORY") or
            ($REGION-docker.pkg.dev/$PROJECT/$REPOSITORY/$IMAGE_NAME"). The
            image name must be the same as the name of the service.

         --source=SOURCE
            The location of the source to build. If a Dockerfile is present in
            the source code directory, it will be built using that Dockerfile,
            otherwise it will use Google Cloud buildpacks. See
            https://cloud.google.com/run/docs/deploying-source-code for more
            details. The location can be a directory on a local disk or a
            gzipped archive file (.tar.gz) in Google Cloud Storage. If the
            source is a local directory, this command skips the files specified
            in the --ignore-file. If --ignore-file is not specified, use
            .gcloudignore file. If a .gcloudignore file is absent and a
            .gitignore file is present in the local source directory, gcloud
            will use a generated Git-compatible .gcloudignore file that
            respects your .gitignored files. The global .gitignore is not
            respected. For more information on .gcloudignore, see gcloud topic
            gcloudignore.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --binary-authorization=POLICY
          Binary Authorization policy to check against. This must be set to
          "default".

       --clear-binary-authorization
          Remove any previously set Binary Authorization policy.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --clear-encryption-key-shutdown-hours
          Remove any previously set CMEK key shutdown hours setting.

       --encryption-key-shutdown-hours=ENCRYPTION_KEY_SHUTDOWN_HOURS
          The number of hours to wait before an automatic shutdown server after
          CMEK key revocation is detected.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --clear-key
          Remove any previously set CMEK key reference.

       --key=KEY
          CMEK key reference to encrypt the container with.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --clear-labels
          Remove all labels. If --update-labels is also specified then
          --clear-labels is applied first.

          For example, to remove all labels:

              $ gcloud beta run deploy --clear-labels

          To remove all existing labels and create two new labels, foo and baz:

              $ gcloud beta run deploy --clear-labels \
                --update-labels foo=bar,baz=qux

       --remove-labels=[KEY,...]
          List of label keys to remove. If a label does not exist it is
          silently ignored. If --update-labels is also specified then
          --update-labels is applied first.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --labels=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          List of label KEY=VALUE pairs to add.

          An alias to --update-labels.

       --update-labels=[KEY=VALUE,...]
          List of label KEY=VALUE pairs to update. If a label exists, its value
          is modified. Otherwise, a new label is created.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --clear-network
          Disconnect this Cloud Run service from the VPC network it is
          connected to.

       Direct VPC egress setting flags group.

         --network=NETWORK
            The VPC network that the Cloud Run service will be able to send
            traffic to. If --subnet is also specified, subnet must be a
            subnetwork of the network specified by this --network flag. To
            clear existing VPC network settings, use --clear-network.

         --subnet=SUBNET
            The VPC subnetwork that the Cloud Run service will get IPs from.
            The subnetwork must be /26 or larger. If --network is also
            specified, subnet must be a subnetwork of the network specified by
            the --network flag. If --network is not specified, network will be
            looked up from this subnetwork. To clear existing VPC network
            settings, use --clear-network.

         At most one of these can be specified:

           --clear-network-tags
              Clears all existing network tags from the Cloud Run service.

           --network-tags=[TAG,...]
              Applies the given network tags (comma separated) to the Cloud Run
              service. To clear existing tags, use --clear-network-tags.

     At most one of these can be specified:

       --clear-post-key-revocation-action-type
          Remove any previously set post CMEK key revocation action type.

       --post-key-revocation-action-type=POST_KEY_REVOCATION_ACTION_TYPE
          Action type after CMEK key revocation.
          POST_KEY_REVOCATION_ACTION_TYPE must be one of:

           prevent-new
              No new instances will be started after CMEK key revocation.
           shut-down
              No new instances will be started and the existing instances will
              be shut down after CMEK key revocation.

GCLOUD WIDE FLAGS
    These flags are available to all commands: --access-token-file, --account,
    --billing-project, --configuration, --flags-file, --flatten, --format,
    --help, --impersonate-service-account, --log-http, --project, --quiet,
    --trace-token, --user-output-enabled, --verbosity.

    Run $ gcloud help for details.

NOTES
    This command is currently in beta and might change without notice. This
    variant is also available:

        $ gcloud run deploy

